(
"ai_sub_version": "1.11.0",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 3,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false
)
hololive English -Promise- 2nd Anniversary Concert: Promise 2 You
アスファルト タイヤを切りつけながら
Asphalt, while the tires cut into it
暗闇走りぬける
Racing through the darkness
チープなスリルに身をまかせても
Even if I surrender myself to cheap thrills
明日におびえていたよ
I was afraid of tomorrow
It's your pain or my pain or somebody's pain
誰かのために生きられるなら
If I can live for someone's sake
It's your dream or my dream or somebody's dream
なにもこわくはない
Nothing is scary anymore
Get wild and tough
ひとりでは解けない愛のパズルを抱いて
Holding the puzzle of love that can't be solved alone
Get wild and tough
この街でやさしさに甘えていたくはない
In this city, I don't want to rely on kindness
Get chance and luck
君だけが守れるものがどこかにあるさ
There's something somewhere that only you can protect
Get chance and luck
ひとりでも傷ついた夢を取り戻すよ
Even alone, I'll take back the wounded dream
Promise -hololive English-
Steppin' out
Lyrics: Kohshi Asakawa   Music: Takeshi Asakawa
ありきたりな僕の
My ordinary...
日々を壊してくれ
...days, destroy them for me.
異常なほどの刺激を
An extraordinary level of stimulation...
待ち望んでいたがな
...is what I've been waiting for.
ちょっとしたその冒険心は
That slight sense of adventure...
改札に吸い込まれて
...is sucked into the ticket gate...
吐き出され辿り着いた
...spat out, and I arrived at...
雨降るこの街
...this rainy city.
何も感じないまま
Without feeling anything...
死んでいくのはごめんだ
...I refuse to just die.
終わりのその先も
Beyond the end...
目指して
...I'll aim for.
駆け出せ Steppin' out tonight
Dash out, steppin' out tonight.
僕らは不確かなまま
While we remain uncertain.
輝く Steppin' out tonight
Shining, steppin' out tonight.
待ってるんだぜ明日が
Tomorrow is waiting for us.
抗え Steppin' out tonight
Resist, steppin' out tonight.
僕らは風の中
We are in the wind.
それでも Steppin' out tonight
Even so, steppin' out tonight.
追いかけてんだ
I'm chasing after it.
So there's no looking back
混ざる火を突っ込んで
Plunging into the mingling fire...
見事に散らかしてんだ
...I'm scattering it beautifully.
曖昧で退屈な
Farewell to these vague...
気持ちとさらばさ
...and boring feelings.
関係ないって顔したって
Even if you act like it doesn't matter...
どこかで繋がっていて
...we're connected somewhere.
何度だって引き戻す
It'll pull you back time and again...
手招くこの街
...this beckoning city.
ビリビリしびれるような
Like a tingling numbness...
今を生きていたいんだ
...I want to live for the now.
極限のギリギリで
On the very edge of the limit...
行こうぜ
...let's go.
駆け出せ Steppin' out tonight
Dash out, steppin' out tonight.
僕らは不確かなまま
While we remain uncertain.
輝く Steppin' out tonight
Shining, steppin' out tonight.
待ってるんだぜ明日が
Tomorrow is waiting for us.
抗え Steppin' out tonight
Resist, steppin' out tonight.
僕らは風の中
We are in the wind.
それでも Steppin' out tonight
Even so, steppin' out tonight.
追いかけてんだ
I'm chasing after it.
So there's no looking back
Inside, outside...
...just wanna feel good every day
Inside, outside, I just wanna feel good every day
Inside, outside, I just wanna feel alive
駆け出せ Steppin' out tonight
Dash out, steppin' out tonight.
僕らは不確かなまま
While we remain uncertain.
輝く Steppin' out tonight
Shining, steppin' out tonight.
待ってるんだぜ明日が
Tomorrow is waiting for us.
抗え Steppin' out tonight
Resist, steppin' out tonight.
僕らは風の中
We are in the wind.
それでも Steppin' out tonight
Even so, steppin' out tonight.
追いかけてんだ
I'm chasing after it.
So there's no looking back
[A]ddiction
Lyrics: Reol   Music: Giga
Don't take your love away, wait, not yet, yeah yeah
Don't take your love away, wake up, make up, bang!
また鳴り出した表示は あなた「今忙しいの」
The display started ringing again, it's you, "I'm busy right now."
Liar...
未読の毒とラブコール いっぱいで世話しないじゃん
Full of unread poison and love calls, it's so restless.
邪魔をしないで頂戴
Please don't get in my way.
最後にくれた「可愛ええ」 内成る意向ですね
The "cute" you gave me last, it's an internal intention, isn't it?
踏んで また足掻きね
Step, and struggle again
本音は言わない方が やらしい
It's more suggestive if you don't speak your mind
甘い言葉かけるよりも
Rather than whispering sweet words
ずっと愛おしい
It's far more precious
たまらなくなるほど
So much that it's unbearable
求めて 離さないで
Crave me, don't let me go
キスじゃ足りなくて
A kiss isn't enough
いっそ 狂わせて
Rather, drive me mad
Predilection あなたを手に掛けて
Predilection, taking you in my hands
Infatuation 呼吸さえ止めて
Infatuation, even stopping your breath
Dedication このまま[A]ddiction して
Dedication, just like this, getting addicted
まだたった一口で終い
Just one more bite and it's over
Predilection さあ口を着けて
Predilection, come, put your lips to it
Infatuation そのまま飲み込んで
Infatuation, just swallow it down
Dedication すぐさま[A]ddiction して
Dedication, instantly getting addicted
ほらたった一口 死ぬほど愛したいだけで
See, just one bite, I just want to love you to death
Look at the way when you wear nothing yet
Oh don't take your love away
Wake up, wake up, bang bang!
Ooh have it all 愛情が足りない
Ooh have it all, there's not enough love
あなたには私しかいない
You have no one but me
Ooh take it off 愛情が足りない
Ooh take it off, there's not enough love
私にはあなたしかいない
I have no one but you
踏んで 満たした この手掴んだ
Stepped, filled, grabbed these hands
まだ未練があるのね あなたは
You still have regrets, don't you?
わがまま 愛と名付けて
Selfishness, calling it love
また支配する
I'll rule over you again
あなたに溺れてく
I'm drowning in you
息苦しいくらいに
So much that it's suffocating
沈静化させて
Quiet me down
いっそ 狂わせて
Rather, drive me mad
Predilection 私を手に掛けて
Predilection, take me in your hands
Infatuation キスで口塞いで
Infatuation, shut my mouth with a kiss
Dedication まだまだ[A]ddiction して
Dedication, still getting addicted
まだたった一口 溺愛
Just one more bite, doting love
Predilection 覗き眼差し混んで
Predilection, peering in with your gaze
Infatuation 躊躇いなど捨てて
Infatuation, throw away your hesitation
Dedication すぐさま[A]ddiction して
Dedication, instantly getting addicted
ほらたった一口 これで終わらせないで
See, just one bite, don't let it end here
Alas, alas
Continued further, evolved more
My love, my love
Is besides with you
Your love, your love
Continued further, evolved more
My more, yes
I'm a little confused
これはアンタのせい 私以外
This is your fault, anyone but me
どこへ行っても 同じ
It's the same wherever you go
腐るほど ただ愛されたかっただけだった
I just wanted to be loved to death
私がいやにならない
Don't grow to hate me
そういう言葉は 期待するだけ無駄だと
Words like that, it's useless to hope for
知ってしまった今 私が分からないよね
Now that I know, you don't understand me, do you?
たまらなくなるほど
So much that it's unbearable
求めて 離さないで
Crave me, don't let me go
キスじゃ足りなくて
A kiss isn't enough
いっそ 狂わせて
Rather, drive me mad
Predilection あなたを手に掛けて
Predilection, taking you in my hands
Infatuation 呼吸さえ止めて
Infatuation, even stopping your breath
Dedication このまま[A]ddiction して
Dedication, just like this, getting addicted
まだたった一口で終い
Just one more bite and it's over
Predilection さあ口を着けて
Predilection, come, put your lips to it
Infatuation そのまま飲み込んで
Infatuation, just swallow it down
Dedication すぐさま[A]ddiction
Dedication, instantly getting addicted
さよなら まだ吐き出しで 息が止まるのよ 今
Goodbye, still spitting it out, my breath is stopping now
Life Will Change
Lyrics: Benjamin Franklin Music: 目黒将司
Lyrics: Benjamin Franklin Music: Shoji Meguro
It's not a game
I'm not a robot AI
challenging you
I'm not a phantom
I'm in your face and
I'm here to see it through
Right before your eyes
Watch us multiply
Come to claim our rights
It's time
As our power grows
Try to stop our shows
Might as well go try
Stop time
So you know that we're out there
Swatting lights in the making
I can move fast without breaking
Can't hold on or life will change
And our voices ring out yeah
Took the mask off to feel free
Fought it out in the debris
Now we know that life will change
And it's time,
I'm not a figment on your ailing old mind
I'm just as real as,
I'm just as dangerous as you so know you'll find
A taste of your own meds
Fire in every breath
Fire inside your head, your home
And as you triple threat
Try to fight in vain
Your empire of... oh...
And you'll know we were out there
Swatting flies in the making
Your empire for the taking
Can't hold on or life will change
And our voices ring out yeah
Took the mask off to feel free
Fought it out in the debris
Now we know that life will change
X-encounter
Lyrics: 黒崎真音 Music: 高瀬一矢
Lyrics: Maon Kurosaki Music: Kazuya Takase
飛べない 此処からじゃ
I can't fly from here
横顔 眺めているだけじゃ
If I'm just staring at your profile
無力さ 嘆いても
Even if I lament my helplessness
この背を 誰も押さない
No one will push me forward
Going out
飛び方を忘れていた
I'd forgotten how to fly
雛鳥たちの嘆きのVoice
The voice of the chicks' lamentations
凍てつく無機質な世界に何を望むの？
What do you hope for in this frozen, inorganic world?
そうだよね 確実な希望が僕の中に
That's right, a certain hope is inside of me
Going out
何ができるかなんてのはやってみなきゃわからない
You won't know what you can do until you try
走り出した 始まりへ
I've started running toward the beginning
きっと 生まれる前から決まっていた
It was surely decided before I was born
羽を揺らし 強く地面を蹴って
Flapping my wings and kicking off the ground
君の元へ 羽ばたけ
I'll fly to you
Ravens, spiraling, holding on
螺旋のルートの中で会う
Meeting within the spiral route
この場所でもう止められない
I can't be stopped in this place anymore
カルマの真下で僕にできることが
What I can do right beneath karma
どんなに僅かでも
No matter how little it is
その身体に背負うもの その痛み 分け合える日まで
The things you carry on that body, until the day we can share that pain
君のそばにいる
I will be by your side
...よう 飛び立つ今
...to fly away now
X-encounter
無性に振り返る 自分の居場所探して
Recklessly looking back, searching for my place
後悔になぞらえた もろい生 蝕む夜にいた
Tracing my regrets, I was in a night that erodes my fragile life
不器用に風に揺れて 僕はまだ弱いままで
Clumsily swaying in the wind, I am still weak
迷って壊れては そうやって続く世界へ
Lost and broken, towards the world that continues like that
たった一つ見つけたら 瞬く星を描き進め
If you find just one thing, keep drawing the twinkling stars as you move forward
闇から覗いた光 手を伸ばして さあ行こう
The light peeking from the darkness, reach out your hand and let's go
走り出したこの思い ほら心の星が導いて
This feeling that started running, look, the star in my heart is leading the way
染み付いてる言えない傷を この翼で
The unerasable scars that have set in, with these wings
運び出せ Brave...
Carry them out, Brave...
I keep holding on 雲を切り 形のない涙も蹴散らして
I keep holding on, cutting through the clouds, scattering even the shapeless tears
凛とした目に宿る灯火を 曇らせはしない
The light dwelling in your dignified eyes, I will not let it cloud over
君はそのままでいて
Stay just as you are
向かい風に逆らい いざ羽広げ目指そう 僕ら果てる日まで
Defying the headwind, now spread your wings and aim for it, until the day we perish
共にかけて行こう X-encounter
Let's run together, X-encounter
誰のせいでもない涙 誇りにして さあ行こう
The tears that are no one's fault, take pride in them and let's go
走り出す始まりへ きっと生まれる前から決まっていた
Running towards the beginning, it was surely decided since before I was born
羽を揺らし強く地を蹴って 君の元へ
Shaking my wings and kicking the ground hard, to where you are
羽ばたけ Brave...
Fly away, Brave...
I keep holding on 幾千の後悔の後に息吹く鼓動
I keep holding on, the heartbeat that breaths after thousands of regrets
この一瞬が永遠へ変わる 手を繋ぎそして世界を見に行こう
This moment turns into eternity, hold hands and let's go see the world
皮肉にも僕たちは 抗いより潜り抜け知るんだろう
Ironically, we will probably know by slipping through rather than resisting
生存の意味を 真実へと駆けて行こう
The meaning of existence, let's run towards the truth
遠回り それは幸福への景色にも
A detour, even that becomes a scenery towards happiness
愛を持てた時に 世界はまた生まれ変わる
When you can have love, the world will be born again
（歓声）
(Cheering)
Thank you so much for watching the anniversary live!
So far! Are you guys having a good time?
Don't forget to share your comments using the...
...hashtag shown at the top right of the screen!
#Promise2U!
This way!
No, this way!
#Promise2U!
All right, we're currently at the Promise Hideout!
Whoo! / Yeah!
Over there...
Oh my God, that is huge!
Right?!
Oh my God, it's so pretty!
Look at those ads from over there!
Whoa, I'm way too excited!
No, you guys!
Don't die! Don't die!
No, it's so big! Hello!
Hello everyone! Is there a helicopter flying out there taking videos of us? Whoa!
Now we have it. Now we do.
And now that we also have such a fancy stage on the rooftop as well...
...and everything, let's turn things up with some fun...
...variety games!
Variety games!
Yes, it's a variety part!
Yeah, I bet you guys are probably feeling a bit tired...
...after that intense first half of this live, right?
I'm good! I'm there, I'm alive, I'm standing! No, we're good!
No, you guys seem a bit tired. Yeah.
To help you recover from that fatigue and tiredness...
...I've prepared the perfect segment for you guys.
Yes, it's called...
Pleasure or Pain? Promise Foot Massage Karaoke Battle!
What does that mean?
Did she say feet?
Rules: Each member will sing one chorus from two songs they're good at! Battle it out by total score using the scoring system.
Each of us will sing the choruses from two songs that we're confident in!
Yes, we'll use the karaoke machine's scoring system...
...and the person with the highest combined score will win!
Rules: Foot pressure point massage while singing... Can they hold out and finish the song?
There's also a twist!
I knew it!
Yes, we will be singing while receiving foot massages!
Wait, what?
And how that will affect our performance or score, well...
...we'll see and find out together! Right here!
Yes, and there'll be a punishment for the losers as well, of course.
Rules: Place 2nd or lower and drink the super sour geki-suppa juice as punishment!
Two losers, right? I'm pretty sure that's how it is, yeah.
And as for the punishment, the losers will have to drink...
...this super sour geki-suppa drink!
Geki-suppa juice?
Geki-suppa juice! Whoa!
Now let me show you the key item that could make or break this battle!
Here's what we'll use for the first round! Da-da-dang!
First Half: Foot Reflexology Mat
It's a foot reflexology mat!
I've never stepped on one of these before.
I have. Oh, it's not pleasant.
It's not fun, yeah.
Wait, so you want us to... wait, we're singing while we're on this?
You're gonna sound amazing. We're all gonna sound amazing singing on this, yes.
So, who's brave enough to go first?
Senpai! Senpai! Senpai!
Senpai, I feel like, you know, you look so beautiful today.
That's why it's got to come out from complementing me like...
...oh, you look, you look so amazing! Oh my God!
Don't you know? I feel like as a senpai, you should show us how it's done, right?
Fine! I'll go first! Okay, fine!
I'll show you how it's done! Yes!
All right, so IRyS, which song are you gonna sing?
I am going to sing Zankyo Sanka.
Oh! Zankyo Sanka! Yes!
If you're ready! Get on the mat!
Let's go! I gotta get on the mat, get on the mat, get on the mat!
Ah... come on, come on...
Don't be dramatic.
Oh! It's spicy!
Oh! It's spicy! Oh! This sucks! Ah!
Music, go! Start! It's not so bad.
You have to do this! Yes you do.
ハイ最高！始まりよ！いこう！
Yes, awesome! It's starting! Let's go!
誰が袖に咲く幻花
Whose illusory flower blooms on the sleeve?
ただそこに藍を落とした
Simply dropping indigo there
派手に色を溶かす夜に
On a night where colors melt flamboyantly
銀朱の月を添えて
Accompanied by a vermilion moon
転がるように風を切って
Cutting through the wind as if rolling
躓くごとに強くなった
Becoming stronger with every stumble
光も痛みも怒りも全部
All the light, pain, and anger
抱きしめて
Embrace them all
選ばれなければ選べばいい
If not chosen, then just choose yourself
声よ轟け　夜のその向こうへ
Let your voice roar beyond the night
涙で滲んでた
It was blurred with tears
あんなに遠くの景色まで　響き渡れ
Even to that landscape so far away, resound throughout
何を奏でて？誰に届けたくて？　不確かなまままでいい
What are you playing? Who do you want to reach? It's okay to remain uncertain
どんなに暗い感情も
No matter how dark the feelings
どんなに長い葛藤も　歌と散れ　残響
No matter how long the conflict, scatter with the song, reverberation
Oh, IRyS!
I can barely balance!
You need good blood, right? Good blood.
Oh, there you go.
Oh my god, that hurt.
How's your blood flow? Do you feel...
...how do you... do you feel refreshed?
You look great.
Alright! Looks like the score is in.
Shall we see the score?
Oh, the score!
Alright, this is what she got! Ta-da!
1st Challenge 70.161 pts.
I've never... I've never gotten a score that low before!
70.161! That's so, so good!
That's good!
It's not... That's good? What are you talking about?
You know, 70, that's a... that's a... C?
No, B.
That's a B. That's a B-minus.
B-minus. B-minus. Yeah, that's good.
Is it a B-minus? That's a C. That's a C-minus.
No, no, no... it's a B-minus.
It's a B-minus.
Alrighty then. Who wants to go next?
Senpai! Senpai!
先輩じゃないよ！
I'm not your senpai!
We're from the same... she's senpai by two hours.
Was it two hours?
Yeah, I think it was around two hours.
You guys debuted already...
I've never heard that from you before.
Okay, okay, I guess...
Yeah!
I'll go.
I'm gonna have so much fun!
Okay, so Kronii, what song are you gonna sing for us?
Um, I'm going to be singing "Mousouzei".
Whoa! Oh, "Mousouzei"! Yay!
Cause I only know old songs. Yeah!
That's great! I know that song!
Okay then.
Alright, please start the music! Music start-o!
Uh oh, okay.
She sounds confused.
You're gonna be fine. You're gonna be fine.
You're on the edge of the mat, by the way.
あの子もいいな あの子もいいな
She looks good, she looks good too
頭の中でイイコトしてる
I'm doing good things in my head
あなたはそれで満足ですか？
Are you satisfied with that?
叶えたいとは思いいませんか？
Don't you want to make it come true?
You're on a good spot right now.
You're doing good.
She's fine. She's fine, yeah, oh...
あの子でいいや あの子でいいや
She'll do, she'll do
妥協大好き 飲む針千本
I love compromising, I'll swallow a thousand needles
あなたはそれで満足ですか？
Are you satisfied with that?
叶えたいとは思いいませんか？
Don't you want to make it come true?
納めましょう妄想税
Let's pay the delusion tax
皆様の暮らしを 豊かにするために
To enrich everyone's lives
Whoa, she's doing it! She's doing it!
叶えたい たい たいを 現実に
Make what you want to come true a reality
今 未来来来を 買い戻せ
Now buy back the future
アレしたいしたい病も 欲しがりも
The "I want to do that" disease and the greediness
さあ 痛いいたいいたいのに その向こうへ
Come on, beyond the pain
そう 汚い妄想は
Yes, the dirty delusions
汚いお金で解決させましょう
Let's settle them with dirty money
イェーイ！
Yeah!
Whoa! You did amazing! Wow!
I feel like that brought out like a roughness!
Whoa! You could actually sing on that?
Oh, oh wow... blood circulation.
That's a lot of blood circulation.
Oh my god. Wow.
Alright, the score is in! Let's see what Kronii got.
1st Challenge 73.864 pts.
Whoa! Yay!
Wait, wait, it's still first half.
I can still make it. I can still make it.
まだ前半。
Still first half.
Alright, I'll go! My turn!
Yeah! Let's go!
I'm excited! I've been wanting to sing this song for so long.
Okay, what song is it? What are you singing?
フェアリーテイル～約束の日～！
Fairy Tail ~Yakusoku no Hi~!
Finally, I finally found an instrumental track. I'm so excited.
Your childhood, I'm assuming.
Childhood? Not really. Not really. Okay.
Nice Fairy Tail now. Okay, now that you're ready, please hop onto the foot reflexology mat.
Come on... don't fail me, feet.
Ready? You ready? Yeah!
Okay, now please start singing! Music start-o!
Yay!
That stance.
フェアリーテイル この手で掴んだ光は
Fairy Tail, the light I grasped with this hand
Whoa, you're walking! You're walking! Ahhh!
You're great! Yeah, let's go!
夢に描いた 理想郷 夢のまま 終わらせない
The utopia I dreamed of, I won't let it end as just a dream
いつか会える 未来の僕に 伝えたい
I want to tell my future self I'll meet one day
Hai! Hai! Hai! Hai!
時に 未来は残酷で 鏡のように 割れるけど
Sometimes the future is cruel and breaks like a mirror
欠片を 失くさないよう 見つけ出せばいい
I just need to find the pieces so I don't lose them
凍える闇が 僕たちの 行く手 塞いでも
Even if the freezing darkness blocks our path
きっと 忘れない 希望
I surely won't forget the hope
フェアリーテイル この手で掴んだ光は
Fairy Tail, the light I grasped with this hand
絆の力 溢れているから
Because it's overflowing with the power of bonds
…溢れているから
...is overflowing
僕らは知っている 悲しい涙を
We know the sad tears
だから譲れない 揺るがない
So we can't give in, won't waver
僕らは知っている 悲しい涙を
We know the sad tears
夢見たあの日に
To that day we dreamed of
そう辿り着くまで
Until we finally reach it
Yo, you guys can sing on this thing.
How was it?
It brings out something from deep within.
From within? Okay then.
Since you have something deep within, it's time to see what score that brought you.
Hai!
1st Challenge
81.434 pts.
Wow! She got an 81.434! Whoa!
Currently in first place is Hakos Baelz...
...with a 81.434 points.
Any comments heading into the second half now?
I'm excited.
I'll continue to do my best...
...so that I don't have to do the juice punishment.
頑張るぞー！
I'll do my best!
All righty then, let me introduce the next key item...
...or should I say person for the second half in this foot massage battle, yeah?
Oh!
では、お入りください。どうぞ！
Now, please come in. This way!
Second Half
Foot Massage Therapist
Whoa!
こんにちは。
Hello.
こんにちは！
Hello!
Okay, let me introduce you guys to Takita-san...
Foot Massage Therapist
Naoko Takita
瀧田泰緒子
Foot Massage Therapist
Naoko Takita
...who will be giving us foot massages. A foot massage pro!
よろしくお願いします。
Nice to meet you.
怖え！
Scary!
怖いね。
Scary, isn't it?
So scary.
痛いですか？
Will it hurt?
痛いです。
It will.
Okay, since it's gonna hurt, who wants to kick things off?
All right, since I went last last time, I'll go first this time.
What are you going to sing?
That is right.
I'm going to be singing "Bakamitai"!
行きます！
Here I go!
Okay then, please get ready.
Takita-san, よろしくお願いします。
Takita-san, please go ahead.
優しくしてください。
Please be gentle.
怖え！
Scary!
大丈夫、健康にいいんだから。
It's okay, it's good for your health.
Let's go!
はい。
Yes.
Okay then, please start the music. スタート！
Okay then, please start the music. Start!
Inner peace...
馬鹿みたい 子供なのね
I'm such a fool, just like a child
夢を追って傷ついて
Chasing dreams and getting hurt
嘘が下手なくせに
Even though you're bad at lying
笑えない笑顔見せた
You showed a smile that couldn't laugh
I love youも ろくに言わない
You barely even said "I love you"
口下手でほんまに不器用
So clumsy and bad with words
なのになのにどうして
And yet, and yet, why...
サヨナラは言えたの
Were you able to say goodbye?
だめだね だめよ だめなのよ
It's no good, no good, it's just no good
あんたが好きで好きすぎて
I love you, I love you too much
どれだけ強いお酒でも
No matter how strong the drink
歪まない思い出が馬鹿みたい
The memories won't distort, I'm such a fool
Oh, that was a beautiful ending to that song.
That is scary, oh my god.
All righty, how was that? How was the song while getting a foot massage?
I can't feel my big toe.
Now the score is in, let's see what you got! じゃじゃーん！
Now the score is in, let's see what you got! Tada!
2nd Challenge
68.057 pts.
You got a 68.057!
It's over 50! So close to a good number, yeah.
痛い、痛い...
It hurts, it hurts...
健康になった。
You've become healthy.
健康になりました。
I've become healthy.
A lot healthier.
Was it really that bad? Oh my god.
You're not exaggerating, are you?
大げさじゃない！
It's not an exaggeration!
やってよ、もう！
Just do it already!
I want, I want to try.
Okay, go go go! But before you sit, what are you going to sing?
I'm gonna sing Usseewa!
All righty, please get ready. 滝田様、またよろしくお願いします。
All righty, please get ready. Mr. Takita, please take care of us again.
お願いします！
Please!
ガチ痛い！ガチ痛い！
It really hurts! It really hurts!
You're done, you're done, you don't have to worry.
Yay!
Okay then, let's go! じゃあ、ミュージック、スタート！
Okay then, let's go! All right, music, start!
思い切りやっちゃって！
Go all out!
正しさとは 愚かさとは
What is right? What is foolishness?
それが何か見せつけてやる
I'll show you exactly what they are
ちっちゃな頃から優等生
I've been a model student since I was small
気づいたら大人になっていた
Before I knew it, I'd become an adult
ナイフの様な思考回路
With a mind like a knife
持ち合わせる訳もなく
I didn't have the means to use it
でも遊び足りない 何か足りない
But I haven't played enough, something's missing
困っちまうこれは誰かのせい
It's a problem, and it's someone's fault
あてもなくただ混乱するエイデイ
Just aimlessly confused every day
それもそっか 最新の流行は当然の把握
I guess so. Of course, I'm on top of the latest trends
経済の動向も通勤時チェック
Checking economic trends during my commute too
純情な精神で入社しワーク
Joining the company with a pure spirit and working
社会人じゃ当然のルールです
It's a natural rule for a member of society
はぁ？
Ha?
うっせぇうっせぇうっせぇわ
Shut up, shut up, shut up!
あなたが思うより健康です
I'm healthier than you think
一切合切凡庸な
Everything is just mediocre
あなたじゃ分からないかもね
You might not understand
嗚呼よく似合う その可もなく不可もないメロディー
Ah, it suits you well, that melody that's neither good nor bad
うっせぇうっせぇうっせぇわ
Shut up, shut up, shut up!
頭の出来が違うので問題はナシ
Our brains are built differently, so no problem
すごい！ Wow! Yay!
Amazing! Wow! Yay!
ありがとうございます。
Thank you very much.
It felt like you were in a massage.
Yeah, I feel so good! Yay!
え、マジ？
Wait, seriously?
All righty then, the score's in again. Let's see what you got. 結果をお願いします、ジャジャーン！
All righty then, the score's in again. Let's see what you got. Result please, jajan!
2nd Challenge: 77.994 pts.
She got a 77.994, that's literally a 78.
All right, well, who's left? We only have one person left.
IRyS先輩！
IRyS-senpai!
行きなさい、早く。
Go on, hurry up.
What song are you singing?
I am going to be singing Akuma no Ko because the world is just that cruel. 世界は残酷です。
I am going to be singing Akuma no Ko because the world is just that cruel. The world is cruel.
先生も本当に思い切りやってください。
Teacher, please really go all out.
優しくしてください。
Please be gentle.
強く、強く。
Stronger, stronger.
All right, you ready? I'm scared.
Yes, じゃあ、ミュージック、スタート！
Yes, all right, music, start!
鉄の弾が正義の証明
Iron bullets are the proof of justice
貫けば英雄に近づいた
If they pierce through, I'm closer to being a hero
その目を閉じて触れてみれば
If you close your eyes and try to touch
同じ形 同じ体温の悪魔
A devil of the same shape and body temperature
僕はダメで あいつはいいの？
I'm no good, but they are?
そこに壁があっただけなのに
Even though there was just a wall there
生まれてしまった運命嘆くな
Don't lament the fate of being born
僕らはみんな自由なんだから
Because we are all free
鳥のように羽があれば
If I had wings like a bird
どこへだって行けるけど
I could go anywhere
帰る場所がなければ
But if I have no place to return to
きっとどこへも行けない
I surely can't go anywhere
ただただ生きるのは嫌だ
I hate just living aimlessly
世界は残酷だ
The world is cruel
それでも君を愛すよ
Even so, I will love you
なにを犠牲にしても
No matter what I sacrifice
それでも君を守るよ
Even so, I will protect you
間違いだとしても
Even if it's a mistake
疑ったりしない
I won't doubt it
正しさとは自分のこと強く信じることだ
Righteousness is believing in yourself strongly
だろう？ How was... how do you feel? Refreshing, right?
Right? How was... how do you feel? Refreshing, right?
That was great!
素晴らしい体験をさせていただきました。痛っ。
Thank you for the wonderful experience. Ouch.
All right, I feel like the scores are in. Shall we see? ジャジャーン！
All right, I feel like the scores are in. Shall we see? Jajan!
2nd Challenge: 77.716 pts.
And that concludes the second half!
My big toe still hurts so bad.
Yeah, みんな痛がってます。滝田さん、ありがとうございました。
Yeah, everyone's in pain. Mr. Takita, thank you very much.
ありがとうございました！痛気持ちよかったです。バイバイ！
Thank you very much! It hurt but it felt good. Bye-bye!
Okay then, I present to you the final scores!
Dadang! Dadang!
The one and only first place...
...with 151,858 points is Ouro Kronii!
Champion: Ouro Kronii
The healthiest of us all!
How do you feel? How do you feel?
Oh, I wish I got a massage for my left side too, that would have been so nice.
But you know, I'm so happy that we got to suffer together!
Yeah! Woo!
Okay, now with that wholesome moment aside...
Yeah, let's get back to the live!
Not yet! Not yet! No!
But actually, yeah! Let's get back to the live!
No! Not yet! No!
We should get back to the live! Yeah, I think it's time, yeah!
It's time for the punishment game!
Staff-san, please prepare! Thank you, thank you!
Okay, so they said it was like a super sour drink?
Yeah, I heard it's a sour drink.
It smells... it smells healthy! Oh wait, it smells good though!
It smells like ass.
Mmm! It's like... like ume, maybe?
Mmm! It's like... like plum, maybe?
Is it ume? It smells umey!
Is it plum? It smells plummy!
なんか... 酸っぱくない？ちょっと...
Isn't it... kind of sour? Just a bit...
じゃ、不健康の二人で。
Well then, for the two unhealthy ones.
鯖トースト！乾杯！
Saba Toast! Cheers!
Ahhh! That sounds wonderful!
うめー！
Delicious!
Actually, that's actually really good.
Really? Wow.
Are you good? Yeah, yeah.
酸っぱ... あ、あ... 美味しい。
Sour... oh, ah... It's good.
I'm having a great time! Whoa! It tastes better after a bit more time.
Oh! My face is turning into that lemon meme!
You know that... you know that... with the face just inverts in?
Yeah, that's what's happening.
I feel so... I feel so healthy! So healthy, guys!
So healthy! So healthy! Whooo!
Okay, so we're going to return to the live performance.
And the second half includes new songs, so let's keep it going guys! Woo!
Whoo! Yeah! Let's go back, guys!
Yeah, you guys are fine. Okay, let's get a move on.
Yes, yes, let's just get a move on. Alright.
Whoo! Oh! You still? You really? I'm fine now.
だいぶ... だいぶよくなったよ。
Much better... I feel much better now.
ダイダイダイダイダイキライ
Lyrics, Music: Amala
Dai dai dai dai dai kirai
全部 全部 あんたのせいで
It's all, all because of you
ヘドが出るくらいに
To the point I want to vomit
惨憺は 何度 願って 縋って
Misery, no matter how many times I prayed, clung
期待したって 確か 馬鹿だったわ
And hoped, I was surely a fool
幽幻 互いのアップルビジョン
Ethereal, each other's Apple Vision
ブレインにアンチない一生
A life without anti-vision in the brain
義理に 浅いキャパシティ 毎度 ギリ
Capacity shallow in duty, every time barely
詰まるとこ人生 ずっと地味
In the end life is always plain
忌々しい 痛々しい
It's annoying, it's painful
無視できないのが いっそ 腹立たしい
It's rather irritating that I can't ignore it
苛々しい そろそろ飽きた
It's aggravating, I'm getting tired of it soon
自画自賛に
Of the self-praise
だから ライドの反対はアブシー
So, the opposite of ride is Abusi
年功序列なんてバクシー
Seniority system is just Baxy
切り離せない関係性
An inseparable relationship
走ってしまいたいわ
I want to just run away
これは 祝祝 揺るる
This is celebration, swaying
どうし 匿名性の声明を
Friends, an anonymous statement
声明に 乗せてんだ
Putting it into a statement
何を学んだいたいだ
What did I learn, ouch
気が付いた右に倣え
I realized, follow the leader
悪信号にずっと心酔です
I've been fascinated by the bad signal all along
大体 あなたのこと 私
For the most part, regarding you, I
ダイダイダイダイダイキライ
Hate you really, really, really, really, really much
オーマイガー 情けない
Oh my god, how pathetic
もはや バイバイバイバイバイしたい
I want to say bye bye bye bye bye already
脳内 もう予想苦の
In my brain, already predictable
故に 改改改改改は無い
Therefore there is no revision
大体 私のこと あなた
For the most part, regarding me, you
ダイダイダイダイダイキライ
Hate me really, really, really, really, really much
なんてさ 愛を 向かい合って
Just kidding, facing love
1人無し
All alone
ナッシング もしもし 奪われ
Nothing, hello hello, if I get used
慣れれば デモに 懲りらしい
To being deprived, I'll be fed up with the demo
愛ミスして 近付いて
Mistaking love, getting closer
躓きは ボンミスに
The stumble becomes a blunder
サンキュー 半目凝視
Thank you, staring with half-open eyes
跡形消えていく位は
To the point the traces disappear
よしよし いい子で
There, there, being a good kid
笑顔振り撒き バラバラ いい子ね
Scattering smiles, being a good kid separately
だけど だけど その本性は
But, but, your true nature
善悪の区別も付かないの
Can't even tell the difference between good and evil
現今の色彩通り
According to modern colors
感情に任せて
Leave it to your emotions
障害 ダイダイダイ キライな
For a lifetime, I hate you so much
あなを どうせ 悔いくらっちゃった
I've ended up regretting it anyway
人は鏡なんです
People are mirrors
実の所 依存を両円です
In reality, dependence is a good match
シャットダウンしても 隙間と
Even if I shut down, the gaps and
己の様子が不甲斐ない
My own state are pathetic
全部 全部 あんたのせいで
It's all, all because of you
ヘドが出るくらいに
To the point I want to vomit
…まんないわ
...not gonna stop
いっそのこと切り放した方が楽なのだ
It'd be easier just to cut ties altogether
大嫌いあなたのこと私だいだいだいだい大嫌い
I hate you, I really, really, really, really hate you
お前が情けないもはやバイバイバイバイバイしたい
You're pathetic, I want to say bye-bye-bye-bye-bye already
脳内もう嘘吐き上に買い買い買い買い買わない
My brain is full of lies, I'm not buying into it any-any-any-any-anymore
どうだ？私のことあなただいだいだいだい大嫌い
How's that? You really, really, really, really hate me too, don't you?
ほらさ愛してやって一に流しな今に今にしからばなればでもにニコチなし
Look, just love it and let it go, soon, soon, if that's the case, then no nicotine
愛して自画ついて結末はボミスボミスサンキューあめんきょし
Love it, get stuck on your ego, the end is a mistake, mistake, thank you, no license
後味最悪だく無いわ！
It's not like the aftertaste is the absolute worst!
Oh
HALF / Lyrics, Music: 薔薇園アヴ
HALF / Lyrics, Music: Queen Bee Avu-chan
Uh-huh
Yeah
Yeah!
I'm not into what you're wanting
I'm gonna express myself in this song
H-A-L-F
簡単な英語しかわかんない
I only know simple English
踊るの大好き健康第一
I love to dance, health comes first
憧れとコンプレックス大渋滞
A heavy traffic jam of admiration and complexes
滑走でノリノリ滑走は飽き飽き
Rolling on the runway, I'm tired of the runway
邪魔されてるいつもいつでも
Being hindered always, at all times
恵まれているかどうかを
Whether I'm blessed or not
楽しく過ごしていたい泣きたくないから
I want to spend my time happily because I don't want to cry
問い質す神様がいなくても
I'll keep questioning even if there's no God
もうカッコつけていくしかないじゃん
There's no choice but to keep acting cool
そのままこのまま降り注ぐ光ね
Just as it is, like this, the light pouring down
半分なんて思ったことないぜ
I've never thought of it as just half
そのままそのまま突き進む光
Just as it is, pushing forward through the light
意地悪なんかじゃ止まんない
Meanness won't stop me
笑わせたいのに上手にできない
I want to make you laugh but I can't do it well
誰かのせいにはしたくないよ
I don't want to blame it on someone else
生まれてみたいから生まれてきただけ
I was just born because I wanted to be born
新しい普通と幸せ
A new normal and happiness
そんなに遠くはないでしょう
It's probably not that far away
それでも今も誰かが撃ち放つ
Still, even now, someone lets loose
悲しみと怒りのH-A-L-F
The sadness and anger of H-A-L-F
損をしたりしょっちゅう辛い
Losing out or feeling miserable all the time
そんな日もあるけれど
There are days like that, too
茨の道で花が咲くなら
But if flowers bloom on a path of thorns
絶対に見逃せない
I absolutely can't miss it
もうカッコつけていくしかないじゃん
There's no choice but to keep acting cool
そのままこのまま降り注ぐ光ね
Just as it is, like this, the light pouring down
半分なんて思ったことないぜ
I've never thought of it as just half
そのままそのまま突き進む光
Just as it is, pushing forward through the light
X.U.
Lyrics: Benjamin, mpi  Music: Hiroyuki Sawano
I don't want nobody to get killed
I'll come and get you, I am always ready to fight
So don't take all of the blame, we will fight away
Don't take all of the weight you always do
There will always be something you cannot control
We will overcome, your salvation has begun
No signs, no light
Such a mess all over, don't kill your hopes
You make me realize who I need
I'll be there, hold on, they'll change somehow
So where are you now?
I'll reach you, my dawn
Before you can be turned, illusions are torn
The fallen angels you run with don't know
It is our pain that makes us all human after all
Warmth, sepia, photograph, show
Our fragile precious world must protect it, respond to the call
Are they really deep inside your head?
Do they control you like a little marionette?
I'll cut the strings off you dead, come in with me
Let me free the wings of your soul and make it fly
We've been waiting here just to make you whole again
No more hating see, I have always been your friend
Those eyes, no light
Such a mess all over, don't kill your hopes
You make me realize who I need
I'll be there, hold on, they'll change somehow
So where are you now?
I'll reach you, my dawn
The shadows appear, illusions are born
The fallen angels you run with don't know
It is our pain that makes us so human after all
Torn out sepia photograph show
Our fragile precious world must discard it, respond to the call
If you want to fight with me
Then go ahead and fight with me
‘Cause all I want to do is help you man
You will be the death of me
The power of our army has been cut with us all
And if we lose you too, then we may never survive
You can leave, but you must first believe
Just one step at a time and keep your head up boy, and you'll be free
Yay!
How was that so far?
That was good! How did you feel?
It was good.
Do you guys like how it's been going
so far in the songs?
Yay!
We just had all about duo songs?
Yes! Yeah!
And we've also went through the variety part
and everything, yeah.
How are you guys doing? It still hurts.
I don't know how I danced with this way.
How are you guys? You're probably fine.
No, no...
You're fine.
I'm not worried about you at all.
How about you?
My foot still hurts!
But it's okay!
Yay! Persevere!
There's a surprise at the end,
but before that...
Oh!
We have an announcement about merchandise.
Check this out!
Whoo! Yay!
I love the key visual!
It's the Hololive English -Promise-
2nd Anniversary Celebration merch!
We're releasing merchandise
to commemorate our 2nd anniversary!
Let's take turns introducing the merch,
shall we?
Yeah! Yeah!
So first up is a Frame Art Board
of our wonderful key visual
for the Promise 2nd anniversary!
The frame part uses luxurious
sparkling paper
and the printed illustration turns this
into a high-quality piece of art.
Oh my!
You definitely don't want to miss the chance
to add it to your collection or room!
And guess what?
You can even hang it up on the wall!
On the wall?!
Next up are the collection cards
for each of Promise!
These cards feature an attractive design
that are foil stamped on the front,
and you can choose each card individually,
so be sure to collect all of them!
Gotta collect 'em all!
Next we also have ring necklaces!
This design includes cute references
and motifs for each of us.
You can use it as either a ring
or a necklace,
so feel free to change it up
depending on the occasion!
And next we have special porcelain tumblers
with our designs on them!
It features our talent colors
on top of a black base.
They're designed to have a unified look,
and I bet it'll look so cool
if you use several of these tumblers
together in like a drinking party
or something!
Okay, last one!
And lastly, we have a 2-way tote bag!
It's a 2-way design that can be used
as both a shoulder bag and a tote bag.
Oh, that's actually really cool.
It's even designed to be used
as a carry-on bag too,
perfect for traveling and convenience!
And to top it off, it has many pockets
that will definitely be useful
for storing small items like other merch!
Yes! And that concludes the Promise
2nd Anniversary merch introduction!
Yay! Yoroshiku onegaishimasu!
And with that, we're finally
at the very last part.
Sorry for keeping you guys waiting.
We mentioned that there'd be
a special surprise or announcement earlier.
Would you like to hear what it is?
Yes! Yes!
I wonder what it is.
But before we announce it...
It's time for a stage change!
Stage change! Whoo!
Whoa! Wait! What's going on?!
Oh my god, we're floating!
We're going up!
Wait! No!
Don't touch!
Don't touch me!
I'm being touched!
Wait! Hey!
No, IRyS is mine!
No! Wait!
Oh my god!
Don't push!
Okay, okay, we're good, we're good.
Oh!
I'm getting claustrophobic!
Oh, I'm gonna be sick!
Wait! No!
Okay, it's opening!
I see the light!
Oh my goodness.
Okay.
Nice.
Oh, that's nice. I feel fresh air.
All righty. Well, ladies, it is time for our final announcement.
Final announcement? Oh!
We, Promise, have a new original song!
Run Back 'Round
Finally releasing, it's called "Run Back 'Round."
Run Back 'Round! Our brand new! Look at that!
We worked really, really hard on this song, and it's really cool, really catchy.
It's quite different to, you know, a lot of the original songs that we as Promise have put out before.
Different genre.
Yeah, we hope that you guys will listen to it a lot.
The chorus part is quite hype and honestly quite easy to remember.
So I feel like, you know, hopefully it becomes an earworm and you can go put it on loop over and over and over again.
Over and over again. Yeah! That's our big reveal. Hope you're excited.
I'm so excited! Yeah! I'm so excited!
Well, I think, I think all that's left is for us to perform our new song.
What?! We're gonna perform it here?
Right here.
Floating. Floating here. In the city! Yeah! Beautiful!
But before we go, do you have any final thoughts about our live, about our anniversary?
I am just super happy we got to do this as Promise.
And it was a lot of fun singing all those songs with you guys, you know, different duets.
And I just really like the fact that we have a hideout now!
We do! We finally have our hideout now!
We have a venue for celebrations.
Catch you at the bar. Yeah.
And it's in a fabulous location.
Oh, it is too. Imagine how expensive the rent is.
Fabulous! We don't need to pay for it. We don't pay for it. All good.
So, um, yeah, I'm really happy. How about you guys?
Yeah, I'm just really thankful that, you know, we're still here after two years.
And, you know, I hope everyone continues to support Promise. Thank you guys.
And here's to many, many more! Yeah!
I could say the same thing. I'm just gonna steal everyone and say that it's been great being with all of you for two years.
And, you know, now we get to have this cool hideout and this awesome song that we get to show everyone.
So yay! Yay! We ready?
Yeah, I'm ready. Let's go!
Ready, set, go! Run Back 'Round!
Run back 'round...
Run Back 'Round
Lyrics: Steph Music, Arrangement: Vell
Don't stop now...
Run back 'round...
Up with the moonlight,
Down in the streetlights,
Looking for a spotlight,
Making my move.
Whoa... I'm running.
Whoa... 行こう
Whoa... Let's go
Days like a whirlwind,
don't stop coming,
Got me in a tailspin,
What can I do?
Whoa... Keep running!
Whoa... 行こう
Whoa... Let's go
Lost and found,
back to where I started,
I won't stay down,
trust me, I can do it!
I live life loud,
take it to the limit,
So stand up proud,
now I'm gonna sing it!
Run back 'round,
it's a new beginning,
I run back 'round,
got to keep believing,
I know where I'm going,
I run back 'round,
nothing's gonna stop me now!
Woah, oh, oh!
I'm gonna run back 'round!
Sparks on the pavement,
Dreams in the distance,
Gotta be relentless,
Faster than sound.
Whoa... Keep running!
Whoa... 行こう
Whoa... Let's go
Oh yeah...
Lock it and load it, 僕らはexplosive
Lock it and load it, we are explosive
Swifter and lighter, 明日もきっとbrighter
Swifter and lighter, tomorrow will surely be brighter
Oh yeah... Faster than lightning, about to get exciting
Keep on running...
Run back 'round, it's a new beginning,
I run back 'round, got to keep believing,
I run back 'round, I know where I'm going,
I run back 'round, nothing's gonna stop me now!
Woah, oh, oh!
止まらないよ！ I'm gonna run back 'round!
I won't stop! I'm gonna run back 'round!
Woah, oh, oh!
走って、走って、走って I'm gonna run back 'round!
Run, run, run, I'm gonna run back 'round!
Woah, oh, oh! 始まるよ I'm coming around,
Woah, oh, oh! It's starting, I'm coming around,
I've got a dream just waiting now I'm gonna run back 'round!
Woah, oh, oh! Yeah, everybody
Yeah, everybody, come on! I'm gonna run back 'round!
Woah, oh, oh!
CAST: IRyS, Ouro Kronii, Hakos Baels
OPENING ANIMATION: Mazu
Foot Massage Therapist: Naoko Takita
CHOREOGRAPHY: Miyuki Nishijima
SPECIAL THANKS: IRyStocrats, Kronies, Brats
EXECUTIVE PRODUCTION: COVER Corp. STUDIO